Byron Tunnell Papers, Inclusive: 1925-1999, undated, Bulk: 1961-1999
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Elected Positions, 1957-1979, undated; 5
  - Texas House of Representatives, 1957-1965, undated; 1
    - 58th Legislature, 1960-1965; 4
      - Topical, Health, PKU, Department of Health and Welfare, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Topical, Law and Order, Criminal Procedure, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Topical, State Finances, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Railroad Commission, 1965-1979; 2
    - General, 1965-1973; 1
      - 75th Anniversary, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Annual Report, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Conference, Texas Mid-Continent Oil and Gas Association, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Conference, West Central Texas Oil and Gas Association, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Invitation, Joint Session of the 59th Legislature Speaker, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Newsletters, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Newsletters, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Newsletters, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Newsletters, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Newsletters, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Oil and Gas Conservation Laws, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Permian Basin Petroleum Appreciation Day, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Resignation, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Rules and Regulations of the Texas RRC Oil & Gas, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Newsletters, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Newsletters, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Topical, Federal Power Commission, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Topical, Texas Committee on Public Education, AFL-CIO, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Topical, Texas Oil Centennial, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Topical, Transportation Division, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Interstate Oil Compact Commission, 1968-1979; 2
      - Annual Meeting, 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Energy Resources Subcommittee, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Environmental Affairs Committee, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Environmental Protection Advisory Committee, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Resolutions Subcommittee, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Texas Oil Journal, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Events, 1943-1997, undated; 6
  Series 6. Events documents Byron Tunnell's event attendance from 1943 to 1997. The series is divided into three subseries: General, Conferences and Conventions, and Texas Inaugurations. The General Subseries includes printed materials, invitations, and other items related to banquets, receptions, luncheons, and reunions. The Conferences and Conventions Subseries consists primarily of travel itineraries, work materials, and personal memorabilia from events such as the National Legislative Conference and the Democratic National Convention where Tunnell served as a Texas delegate. The Texas Inaugurations Subseries houses invitations, programs, and other documents pertaining to Texas inaugural ceremonies. Each subseries is arranged chronologically and is in good condition.
  - General, 1943-1997, undated; 1
    - Invitations, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Tyler High School Commencement Program, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Jaycees, 1957-1970 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Grace Tunnell Marriage Ceremony, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Dinner Invitations, 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Speaker’s Day Gift Books, 1963 April 24 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Commemorations, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Henderson County Historical Survey Committee, 1965 January 17 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Jaycees, Reunion, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Washington’s Birthday Celebration, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Lyndon B. Johnson Library Dedication, 1971 May 22 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - State Dinner and Ball, 64th Annual National Governor’s Conference, 1972 June 6 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Recognition Luncheon, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Jaycees, Reunion, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Texas Oil Reports, 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Speaker’s Day, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Memorial, Mangum, Preston, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Jaycees, Reunion, 1984-1989 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Memorial, Ramsey, Ben, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Dinner and Dancing, 1987-1991 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Capitol Centennial Celebration, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Committee of State Relations Dinner, 1988 January 25 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Jaycees, Reunion, 1991-1993 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Invitation, Book Signing, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Memorial, Barbeck, Arthur, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Memorial, Connally, John B., 1993 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Jaycees, Reunion, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Memorial, Whitworth, Harry P., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Memorial, Wagstaff, Floyd, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Texas State Cemetery Dedication, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Conferences and Conventions, 1956-1979; 2
    - President’s Conference on Occupational Safety, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - National Legislative Conference, Hawaii (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - National Legislative Conference, Hawaii (2 of 2), 1963 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Democratic National Convention, General, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Democratic National Convention, Hall Passes, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Democratic National Convention, Invitations, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Democratic National Convention, Services, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Democratic National Convention, Texas Delegation, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - National Commission on Constitutional Government (1 of 2), 1964 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - National Commission on Constitutional Government (2 of 2), 1964 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - National Legislative Conference, Atlantic City, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - State Bar of Texas Convention, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Texas State Democratic Convention, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Southern Governors Conference, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Republican Governor’s Association, Winter Conference, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Texas Inaugurations, 1957-1995; 3
    - General, 1957 January 15 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - General, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - General (1 of 2), 1963 January 15 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - General (2 of 2), 1963 January 15 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - General, 1965 January 25-26 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - General, 1967 January 15-17 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - General, 1969 January 20-21 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - General, 1971 January 19 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - General, 1973 January 16 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - General, 1975 January 21 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - General, 1983 January 18 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - General, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - General, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Lobbyist, 1975-1987, undated; 7
  Byron Tunnell resigned his post as Railroad Commissioner of Texas on September 15, 1973, and was appointed vice-president and lobbyist for Tenneco, Inc., an oil and gas company based in Houston, Texas. Materials found in Series 7. Lobbyist, ranging in date from 1975 to 1987, include schedules, notes, newsletters, and presentation slides from Tunnell's work during this time. The folders in this series are arranged in alphabetical order and are in good condition.
  - General, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Daily Schedule, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Historical Review, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Lease, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Legislative Interests, 1986-1987, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Newport News Shipbuilding Launch, U.S.S. Texas, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - South Texas Project, Nuclear Power, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Speech Slides, Lobbying Seminar, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Tenneco 25-Year History and Governmental Affairs Workshop, 1980 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 11)
- Personal, 1948-2005, undated; 8
  The Personal Series is divided into three subseries: General, Awards and Certificates, and Travel. The General Subseries includes political cartoons, guestbooks, day planners, official license plates, and items related to the Jaycees and other personal and business interests. The Awards and Certificates Subseries contains plaques and certificates given to Tunnell by organizations he visited while in office, election certificates from the Texas House and Railroad Commission, the Jaycees, and other civic organizations, as well as commemorative flags flown over the state capitol. The Travel Subseries documents Tunnell’s travel as part of his jobs as well as personal business. Family vacations are mostly documented with itineraries, research material, and small mementos. Each subseries is organized chronologically and is in good condition.
  - General, 1954-2005, undated; 1
    - General, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Biographical Information, IRA Earl Tunnell, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Commemorative Name Tags, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Family, Bette Tunnell, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Hobbies and Recreation, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Jaycees, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Jaycees, Outstanding Young Texans, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Membership Cards, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - “Navy Nightmare” by Lawrence E. Byrum, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Personalized Souvenir “Wanted” Posters, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 13)
    - Political Cartoons, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Political Cartoon, Speaker Re-Election, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Scottish Rite, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Sketch of Tunnell, General Committee on State Relations, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 17)
    - Thank You Note, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Tyler Junior College Caricatures, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Land Deed, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Household Records, 1954-1978, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Bob Bullock Law Practice, 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Bill of Sale, Rio Palm Isle Club, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Political Cartoons, Ben Kaplan, 1960-1964 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Stamford Chamber of Commerce, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Tyler, Texas, 1961-1964, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Speaker’s Day Autographs, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Guestbook, 1963-1965 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Family, Children, 1963-1973 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - State Official License Plate, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Guestbook, Lubbock Visit, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Political Cartoons, Fairness, Bullock’s Raiders, 1966-1976 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 14)
    - Day Planner, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Day Planner, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - State Official License Plate, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Day Planner, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Day Planner (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Day Planner (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Legislative Handbooks and Rosters, 1975-1986 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Day Planner, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Family, John H. Tunnell (Grandfather), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Day Planner, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Tyler High School 35th Class Reunion, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Friday Club, Speeches, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - “Welcome to the Texas House”, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Commemoration Legislation, 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Day Planner, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Tyler High School Caribbean Gathering, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Friday Club, 1980-1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Day Planner, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Friday Club, Speeches, 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Sharon Shrine Temple, 1981-1995 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Day Planner, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Day Planner, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Day Planner, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Texas State Cemetery Application, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Day Planner, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Day Planner, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Day Planner, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Baylor University Alumni Association W. R. White Meritorious Service Award, Correspondence and Programs, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Commemoration Legislation, 1989-1991 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Personalized Oversized Gavel, Presented by Bob Bullock, 1991 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 8)
    - Baylor University Distinguished Alumni, Clippings and Correspondence, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Texas Civil Justice League, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Calendars, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Memorial Service, 2000 March (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Family, Jan Tunnell Oral History, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Awards and Certificates, 1948-1998, undated; 2
    - General, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Plaque, Junior Chamber of Commerce Speak Up Contest, undated (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - General, 1948-1955 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Jaycees, 1953-1964 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - General, 1953-1993, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 12)
    - Pollard Memorial Methodist Church, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Plaque, Service to the Junior Chamber of Commerce, 1955-1957 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - Election Certificate, 1956 November 26 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - General, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Election Certificate, 1958 November 21 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - General, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - General, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - W.C. Windsor Award, Tyler Junior Chamber of Commerce, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Shriners, 1960-1996 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - General, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - General, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Alamo Flag, 127th Anniversary (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Alamo Flag, 127th Anniversary (2 of 2), 1963 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Plaque, Tyler Junior College Ex-Students Association Outstanding Ex-Student, 1963 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - General, 1963-1965 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Election Certificate, 1964 November 20 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - General, 1964-1969 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Railroad Commission, Election Certificates, 1965-1973 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Certificate of Election, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Commemorative Resolutions, 1966-1997 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - General, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Certificate of Election, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - General, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - General, 1980-1999 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Community Service, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - General, 1983-1990 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Texas Inaugural Committee Flag (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Texas Inaugural Committee Flag (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - Plaque, Baylor Alumni Association Distinguished Alumni Award, 1990 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - Plaque, Texas Civil Justice League Achievement Award, 1990 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Plaque, Appreciation from Texas Commission on Alcohol and Drug Abuse, 1996 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Plaque, Baylor University W. R. White Meritorious Service Award, 1998 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Travel, 1962-1997, undated; 3
    - Family Vacation, Mississippi, undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - General, undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - North Dakota, undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Family Vacation, Florida, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Family Vacation, Texas, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - California, 1963 August 24-25 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - New York, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Nevada, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Bahamas, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Texas, 1968-1973 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Alaska, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Ohio, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Rome, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 39)
- Photographs, 1925-1999, undated; 9
  Series 9. Photographs, dated 1925-1999, documents the many facets of Byron Tunnell's life. This series is divided into four subseries: General, Events, Family, and Hunting and Fishing. The General Subseries consists of campaign headshots, group photographs, golf outings, and material from the House floor. The Events Subseries houses items related to Tunnell’s time in office, golf tournaments, travel, meetings, and dedications. The Family Subseries includes family portraits, wedding photos, and Christmas photos. The Hunting and Fishing Subseries follows roughly thirty years of trips Tunnell took with family and friends, including Bob Bullock. Each subseries is in chronological order and in good condition.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Glass plate negative; Photo negative; Photographic print; Portrait photograph
  - General, 1938-1995, undated; 1
    - Byron Tunnell, Speaker of the House, undated (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Campaign Headshots (Glass Plate Negatives), undated (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Dolph Briscoe, Preston Smith, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Gib Lewis and Byron Tunnell, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - Golf Outings, undated (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Group Photos, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Headshots and Group Photos, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - House Chambers, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Panama Canal, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Photo Negatives, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Portraits, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - Shriners, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Texas Capitol, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Texas House, Floor Photos, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - University of Texas Clock Tower, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Herman Brown, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Texas Junior Chamber of Commerce Executive Committee Composite, 1955-1957 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 15)
    - James A. “Jimmy” Turman, 1961-1963 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - 58th Legislature House Composite, Formal Portrait, 1963, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 18)
    - Leisure, 1965-1973 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Travel and Business, 1973-1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Banquets and Business, 1980-1989 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Chamber Photo (circa 1960's), 1981 March 24 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Office Photos and Travel, 1985 January-March (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Travel with Waggoner Carr, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Patsy Middleton, 1990 February 28 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Banquets, 1990-1995 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Events, 1960-1999, undated; 2
    - Lake Trip, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - National Legislative Conference, Hawaii, undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Speaker’s Day, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Swearing-In, undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Texas Trip, undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Royal A. Ferris, Jr. Memorial Reunion (Shriners), 1960 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 19)
    - Inauguration, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Tunnell with Gun from Waggoner Carr’s Collection, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Alaska Trip, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Outing with O.R. Crawford, circa 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Humble Oil Hawkins Dedication, 1971 March (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Golf Tournament, 1971 July (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Perdido Trip, 1971 September (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Golf Tournament, 1972 August (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Wise County 25th Anniversary Celebration, 1973 March (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Legislative Day, 1974 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 20)
    - Speaker’s Day, 1975-1979 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Boat Outing from Clint, 1982 March (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Tyler High School Reunion, 1983-1993 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Boat Trip with Jules Mayer, 1983 August (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Bowers Meeting, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Jaycee Reunion, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Replacing the Goddess of Liberty on Texas Capitol, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Liberty Mutual Legends of Golf Pro-Am, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Oyster Dinner, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Old Gulf, 1987 December (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Boat Outing, 1988 May 9 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Mexico Trip, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Austin Club, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Bowers Meeting, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Speaker’s Day, 1993 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 8)
    - Europe Trip, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Speaker’s Day, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Chili Cookoff, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Tyler High School Reunion, 1998 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 9)
    - Chili Cookoff, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Speaker’s Day, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Family, 1925-1988, undated; 3
    - Byron and Bette Tunnell, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Byron Tunnell, Tunnell’s Father, and Bob Bullock, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Family Portrait, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Byron and Bette Tunnell and daughter, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Family Portraits, circa 1925 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Byron and Bette Tunnell, 1945 January (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - General, circa 1960-1975 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Christmas Photos, circa 1985 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Byron and Bette Tunnell, 1988 June 25 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - General, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Hunting and Fishing, 1965-1992, undated; 4
    - LaTerre Hunting Negatives, undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Fishing Trip, undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Hunting Trip, undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Fishing Trip, 1965 July (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Hunting Trip, circa 1965-1973 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Hunting and Fishing Trip with O.R. Crawford, 1966 June (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Fishing Trip, 1966 October (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Fishing Trip, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Hunting Trip with Dudley Sharp, 1971 July (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Hunting Trip, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Tenneco Hunting Trip, 1981 December 28-30 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Fishing Trip, 1982 September (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Bowers-Spillman Invitational, 1982 December 16-19 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Beevo’s Family Hunt, 1982 December 17-19 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - LaTerre Hunt, 1983 December 27-29 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Caven Hunting Trip, 1984 January 5 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - LaTerre Hunting Trip, 1984 December 28-30 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - LaTerre Hunting Trip, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - LaTerre Hunting Trip, 1986 December 27-30 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Hunting Trip, 1987 January (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Hunting Trip with Bob Bullock, 1987 September (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Hunting Trip, 1987 September 24 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Hunting Trip, 1987 December 7-9 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Hunting Trip, 1987 December 10-13 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Hunting Trip, 1987 December 28 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Caven Extravaganza, 1988 November 9-11 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Hunting Trip, 1989 December 17-18 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Hunting Trip, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Hunting Trip, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Press, 1953-1994, undated; 10
  Series 10. Press contains materials from 1953 to 1994, and is divided into two subseries: News Clippings and Newsletters. Most of the news clippings highlight the work Tunnell did as a member of the Jaycees, when he was serving as a Representative and Railroad Commissioner. Articles related to Bob Bullock are also prominent in the subseries. The newsletters relate primarily to Tunnell's contributions to the Employee Retirement System Board. Both subseries are arranged chronologically and are in good condition.
  - News Clippings, 1953-1999, undated; 1
    - General, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Jaycees, 1953-1969 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - General (1 of 3), 1960-1966 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - General (2 of 2), 1960-1966 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - General, 1970-1977, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - General, 1973 August 29 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - General, 1973 August 30-31 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - General, 1973 September 3-5 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - General, 1973 September 6 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - General, 1973 September 7-13 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - General, 1973 September 18-23 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Bob Bullock, 1986-1999 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters, 1993-1994; 2
    - Pension Observer, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - The Senate Side, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Texas Civil Justice League Advocate, 1993 February (Box 22, Folder 7)